<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on CIPAL ONLINE</title>
    <link>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on CIPAL ONLINE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es</language>
    <copyright>GPL-3.0 license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:22:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducción a los algoritmos y la programación.</title>
      <link>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/introduction-to-algorithms-and-programming/introduction-to-algorithms-and-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/introduction-to-algorithms-and-programming/introduction-to-algorithms-and-programming/</guid>
      <description>¿Qué es un Algoritmo y cómo se diferencia de un Programa? Un algoritmo es un conjunto de instrucciones paso a paso que define cómo se debe realizar una tarea. En la programación, los algoritmos son fundamentales ya que definen la lógica que las computadoras deben seguir para resolver problemas específicos.&#xA;Un programa es la implementación de uno o más algoritmos en un lenguaje de programación específico. Mientras que un algoritmo puede ser representado de muchas maneras, un programa es un artefacto concreto que puede ser ejecutado por una computadora.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guía de Instalación de BSPWM en Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/bspwm-arch-installation-guide/bspwm-arch-installation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 01:56:10 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/bspwm-arch-installation-guide/bspwm-arch-installation-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this guide to install BSPWM in your Arch Linux. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned Linux user or a newcomer, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the process, explain the concepts, and provide tips and tricks to make your experience smooth and enjoyable.&#xA;Important: This guide is based on the assumption that the required packages have been installed using the scripts/initpkg.sh script. Please ensure that you have successfully run this script before proceeding with the steps outlined in this guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guía de Instalación de Arch Linux</title>
      <link>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/arch-installation-guide/arch-installation-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 01:38:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cipalonline.github.io/posts/arch-installation-guide/arch-installation-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this guide to install Arch Linux on your computer. This tutorial is rooted in the official Arch Linux documentation, to ensure that you’re receiving accurate and up-to-date information.&#xA;In addition to the standard procedures, this guide introduces alternative commands and strategies designed to streamline the installation process and cater to your unique preferences. Whether you’re a seasoned Linux user or a newcomer to the world of open-source operating systems, you’ll find these modifications helpful in personalizing your Arch Linux experience.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
